# **ELDAR DADON**

## Industrial engineering and management student

Eldar5120@gmail.com | +972-52-655-3773 | Linkedin: Eldar Dadon

#### **GENERAL**

Industrial engineering and management student in the fourth year with a specialization in information systems. ambitious, responsible, and enjoy beeing a team leader but also great team player. Curious and likes to enrich my knowledge and my peers.

## **EXPERIENCE**

#### security unit of the US Embassy (US Department of state) 2019 -2022

During the work in the security unit of the US Embassy, I performed several-positions, among othrs mangerial positions that include responsibility for a secure. and secure facility, control of personnel, work in different teams, and more

#### Manager at home goods store

The work included inventory management, evaluation of stock orders, management and placement of employees, setting goals, and more.

### Military Service

Combat engineering crops 2016-2019

- platoon sergeant in 605 battalion force.
- courses and certifications: commanding course, slingshot, Sabotage and explosives course.
- conducted trainings and meetings for several ranks between soldier to the commander of the unit.

## **SKILLS**

- SQL
- Python
- Data Engineering
- Algorithmics
- Useing advence AI tools

### **EDUCATION**

#### • Shenkar

2021-present

Undergraduate degree in Industrial Engineering and Management with a specialization in information systems. Third year out of four.

#### • high school education- GYMNASIA REALIT RISHON LEZION.

2013-2016

Complete matriculation certificate, with specialization in geography, physiology and sports psychology

data-bases	Languages	
<ul><li>MySQL</li><li>PANDAS</li></ul>	English	Fluent
	Hebrew	Native